{
    "subject": "resource/American_Vacuum_Society",
    "predicate": "ontology/type",
    "object": "resource/Nonprofit_organization",
    "human_readable": "The American Vacuum Society is a nonprofit organization.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9860338568687439,
            "question": "Is the American Vacuum Society a for-profit organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8933366537094116,
            "question": "What type of organization is the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7730355262756348,
            "question": "Who are the members of the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7105746865272522,
            "question": "How can individuals get involved with the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6779160499572754,
            "question": "What does the American Vacuum Society focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.643560528755188,
            "question": "Are there any events or conferences organized by the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5318931341171265,
            "question": "What is the primary goal of the American Vacuum Society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.52546226978302,
            "question": "How does the American Vacuum Society promote advancements in its field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49668845534324646,
            "question": "Does the American Vacuum Society offer any publications or resources?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41683337092399597,
            "question": "What impact does the American Vacuum Society have on research and development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The American Vacuum Society is a nonprofit organization.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2858_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the American Vacuum Society offer any publications or resources?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2858_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the American Vacuum Society promote advancements in its field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2858_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the primary goal of the American Vacuum Society?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2858_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_139.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2858_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more triples to evaluate!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context information confirms that the American Vacuum Society (AVS) is indeed a non-profit professional society, as mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2858/re-ranker-msmarco/44.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain several references to the American Vacuum Society (AVS) being a non-profit organization. For instance, in `49.txt` and `139.txt`, it mentions that AVS is a non-profit organization. Therefore, the statement \"The American Vacuum Society is a nonprofit organization\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}